Guide to the Timothy Dwight College, Yale University, Scrapbooks
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Timothy Dwight College, Yale University, scrapbooks
1938-1954
RU 876
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
3.5
The records consist of scrapbooks, mostly produced by the Timothy Dwight printshop, documenting activities and residents of Timothy Dwight College, Yale University.
Timothy Dwight College (Yale University)
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 13-G-4 (YRG 13-G-4), Audio-visual materials and memorabilia documenting Timothy Dwight College.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The materials were transferred from the Timothy Dwight College dean's office, 2001.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of scrapbooks, mostly produced by the Timothy Dwight printshop, documenting activities and residents of Timothy Dwight College, Yale University.
College students; Student housing; Scrapbooks; Timothy Dwight College (Yale University); Yale University -- Student housing; Yale University -- Students
- Scrapbooks, 1938-1954; Accession 2001-A-164
  - 1938-1939 (Box 1)
  - 1939-1940 (Box 2)
  - 1940-1941 (Box 3)
  - 1942-1943 (Box 4)
  - 1943-1944 (Box 5)
  - 1946-1948 (Box 6)
  - 1948-1949 (Box 7)
  - 1949-1950 (Box 8)
  - 1950-1951 (Box 9)
  - 1953-1954 (Box 10)
  - 1936-1948 T. D. Press Scrapbook (Box 11)